[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Hello. Welcome to WWDC.
&gt;&gt; 大家好 欢迎来到  WWDC
I'm Brad Jensen and today we're
我是  Brad Jensen
going to be talking about What's
今天我们要说说
New in Location Technologies.
定位技术的新功能
We've got three topics that
我们今天主要谈论
we're going to cover today.
三个话题
First we're going to talk about
首先我们要说说
some miscellaneous API
我们做的各种各样
improvements we've made.
API  的改进
After that we'll talk about our
然后我们将会说到
big change this year, how we've
今年的大变化
revised our authorization and
我们如何修改了授权
usage reporting story, and
以及用户报告
throughout the presentation
在演讲过程中
we'll also touch on best
我们还会根据今年所做的改变
practices given the changes
讲一下最佳案例
we've made this year.
的实践
Now, a word of warning.
现在我提醒一下
This presentation is geared
这个演讲主要针对于
towards developers that are
已经对  Core Location
already familiar with Core
很熟悉的开发者
Location, so if you're new to
所以如果你刚接触
our framework, we recommend you
我们的框架 我们建议你
check out our documentation
回头看下我们的
afterwards.
资料
In addition, our session from
此外 我们去年的会议
last year has a lot of helpful
有很多针对新人的
advice for newcomers.
实用建议
So let's get started.
好我们开始吧
For users of our geocoding API,
对于 geocoding API 的用户
we have some exciting changes
我们为你们准备了一些令人兴奋的
for you.
更新
We've added support for
我们为 Contacts 框架
interoperation with the Contacts
增加了互通性的
framework.
支持
So you can now forward geocode a
所以现在你可以向 geocode 发送
CNPostalAddress.
CNPostalAddress
And additionally, when you get a
并且当你得到了
CLPlacemark result, you can get
CLPlacemark 结果后 你可以从
a CNPostalAddress from that
那个 placemark 得到一个
placemark.
CNPostalAddress
Now, this is meant to be the
现在  这用来
modern replacement for our old
替代对以前的 Address Book
support for the Address Book
框架的
framework.
支持
In particular, you could geocode
更具体讲 你可以 geocode
an address dictionary and get an
一个地址簿
address dictionary out of a
并从 placemark 得到
placemark.
地址簿
On platforms where the Contacts
在 Contacts 框架
framework is available, we're
可用的平台上
deprecating those address
我们在弃用那些
dictionary API's.
地址簿 API
However, on tvOS the Contacts
但是在 tvOS 上
framework isn't available and so
Contacts 框架不可用
you can continue to use those
所以你可以继续使用
address dictionary API's.
那些地址簿 API
We're also adding support for
我们还为有
geocoding with a preferred
偏好语言区的 geocoding 增加了
locale.
支持
This won't impact which results
这不会影响你得到的结果
you get, only which language
只会影响到
they're returned to you in.
他们返回的语言
It's important to note that the
值得注意的是
default behavior for Core
Core Location 的 geocoder
Location's geocoder has always
的默认行为一直是
been to return results in the
使用用户的偏好语言
user's preferred language.
来返回结果
If you specify a preferred
如果你指定了偏好语言区
locale, you are overriding the
你就重写了
user's chosen language
用户选定的
preference.
语言偏好
That might sound bad, but there
这听起来似乎很糟糕
are actually times when it makes
但实际上很多时候却
a lot of sense.
很有用
For example, if you're making a
比如你在做一个
travel guide up, you might want
旅行指南 你可能想要
to display text in your app that
在你的 App 中添加文本
matches the text the user would
并且跟用户在实际生活中
see in the real world.
看到的文本相符
In that case you would want to
在这种情况下你
provide a preferred locale to
向 geocoder 提供
the geocoder that produces
一个偏好语言区
results appropriate for the
产生一个适于顾客
region the user is visiting.
访问区域的结果
We've spent some time improving
我们同样花时间改进了
our heading updates API as well.
我们的 heading 更新 API
Before we get to that, let's
在这之前让我们
just make sure we all understand
确保我们都懂得了
the jargon.
这些术语
Heading refers to the direction
Heading 是指你
that you are facing, and course
面朝的方向
is the direction you're actually
而 course 是你实际上行动的
moving.
方向
Now, with boats and planes you
对于船和飞机来说
tend to see a disconnect between
你可能会看到因为
heading and course due to wind
风和洋流作用 heading 和
or sea currents.
course 不一样
With cars, on the other hand,
另一方面对于汽车来说
you almost never see a
你几乎从未看见
meaningful difference between
heading 和 course 之间
heading and course.
有显著差异
Even if there are very strong
即使有非常猛烈的
winds that push the car to one
风将汽车吹向一边
side or the other, the driver
司机会试图
will tend to compensate.
矫正它
They don't want to get pushed
他们不想被风力推出
out of their lane, or even
他们的车道 更坏的情况是
worse, off the road.
脱离道路
This is a very convenient
这是一个非常便捷的
observation because if we're
观察结果因为当我们在
computing GPS estimates, we're
计算 GPS 大概位置时
very likely to have a good
我们很有可能对设备
estimate of the device's course,
的 course 有个良好的计量
but sometimes computing the
但有时计算 heading
heading can be a little bit more
可能会比较
tricky.
棘手
Even if we're able to accurately
即使我们能正确
estimate the heading of the
测量设备的 heading
device, it might not be the
这也有可能不是
right heading.
正确的 heading
For example, let's suppose the
比如让我们假设
user is navigating in their car
用户在车里导航
and they've mounted their iPhone
他们把他们的 iPhone 放在了
to their dashboard.
他们的仪表盘上
There's a very good chance that
很有可能
they've angled their iPhone to
他们把他们的 iPhone
face themselves, but when they
朝向了自己
do that, they introduce a
当他们这么做时 他们引入了
disconnect between the heading
他们汽车的 heading
of their car and the heading of
与他们 iPhone 的 heading
their iPhone, but when they're
之间的误差 但他们导航时
navigating, they'd really like
他们希望看到
to see the heading of their car.
他们汽车的 heading
Luckily, we just found a really
幸运的是我们找到了
good way to estimate the heading
一个计算汽车 heading
of the car.
的绝佳方式
We can use the course of the
我们可以使用 iPhone 的
iPhone.
course
So in iOS 11 Core Location will
所以在 iOS 11 中 Core Location
now automatically detect
现在可以自动检测
situations where heading and
heading 和 course
course should probably be in
应该一致的情况
agreement and it will leverage
它会权衡
course information to provide a
course 信息来提供
more accurate heading update.
更准确的 heading 更新
It's important to note that this
很重要的一点是当你使用
behavior is fully automatic and
Core Location 的 heading API 时
always on when you use Core
这个行为是完全自动的
Location's heading API.
且一直开启
So if you're creating an app for
所以如果你在为飞机
planes or boats or augmented
或轮船或 AR 开发 App
reality, then you probably want
那么或许你应该
to use Core Motion's
选择使用 Core Motion 的
CMDeviceMotion API instead.
CMDeviceMotion API
Our detection logic is very
我们的检测机制非常优秀
good, but it's not flawless.
但不是完美的
There are times when it will
有时候它也
make the wrong call.
会犯错
If you'd like to learn more
如果你想了解更多
about their API, they had a
他们的 API 他们今年
session this year.
还有个大会
I think it's definitely worth
我觉得非常值得
checking out.
参加
We've also spent a lot of time
我们还花了很多时间
improving our indoor positioning
改进我们的室内
system.
定位系统
As you saw in the keynote, Maps
正如你在 Keynote 看到的那样
will now display floor plans for
Maps 现在会在世界内很多
many indoor venues throughout
室内场馆显示
the world.
楼层指引
At these venues any app that
在这些场馆中所有请求
requests best accuracy location
最准确位置的 App
will automatically receive our
都会自动接收我们的
high accuracy indoor location
高精确度室内位置
estimates.
数据
We have four exciting
今天我还想
improvements that I want to
和大家分享四点
share with you today.
令人兴奋的改进
First, we've improved the
首先我们提升了
accuracy of our estimates.
测量的精确度
Our estimates are GPS quality or
我们的测量达到了 GPS 级别
better.
甚至更好
Second, we've improved the
第二 我们提高了
responsiveness of our indoor
我们室内定位系统
positioning system.
的响应能力
When the user first enters a
当用户刚进入一个
venue, you'll start to receive
场馆后你就会开始接收
those indoor estimates much more
那些室内计量数据
quickly than you did in iOS 10.
比 iOS 10 快的多
We've also improved how quickly
我们还提高了我们
we detect floor transitions.
检测楼层变化的速度
You'll get notified of the new
你得到新楼层
floor more quickly than you did
的通知会比 iOS 10
in iOS 10.
快很多
We've improved the availability.
我们还优化了可用性
And I don't just mean the number
我不仅仅是指
of venues that Core Location
Core Location 支持的
supports.
场馆数
If the user wanders into a
如果用户走进了
region of the venue that maybe
一片未经勘测的
hasn't been surveyed, you'll
场馆区域
still get quality indoor
你还是会通过 Core Location
estimates through Core Location.
得到高质量的室内测量数据
We've improved the
我们还提高了
interoperability of the indoor
室内定位系统和
positioning system with wireless
无线配件之间的
accessories.
互通性
So even if the user is, say,
所以假设用户即使
streaming Beats 1 to their
在通过他们的 AirPod
AirPods, you'll still receive
播放 Beats 1 你还是会
quality indoor location
接收到高质量的室内
estimates.
位置数据
For watchOS we're making our
对于 watchOS 我们在推进
continuous background location
持续的后台位置 API 的
API available.
可用性
You've probably already heard
你可能已经听说过
about this API, but just in
这个 API 了 但万一你没有
case, this API allows your app
这个 API 允许你的 App
to receive location updates even
即使在进入后台时
as it enters the background.
也能接收位置更新
Now, in watchOS 3 it was
现在在 watchOS 3 中
possible to get very similar
也可以通过同时使用
functionality using a
Core Location 和
combination of Core Location and
HealthKit 来实现相似的
HealthKit.
功能了
An HKWorkoutSession would allow
一个 HKWorkoutSession 会允许
your app to continue receiving
你的 App 即使在后台时
location updates even if your
也能持续接收
app was in the background.
位置信息更新
However, we wanted to allow you
但是我们希望
to create new location-based
让你为顾客创造
experiences that weren't
基于位置的新体验
necessarily workout related, and
不一定和健身锻炼有关
so we're bringing our general
所以我们在把我们通用的
purpose continuous background
持续后台位置 API
location API to watchOS.
带到 watchOS 中
Our usual guidance still
我们通常的指导
applies.
仍然适用
This is a fairly power expensive
这是一个相当强大但代价高昂的
API and so you should think
API 所以在使用它之前
twice before using it, but if
你应该仔细考虑
you're creating, say, a
但是如果你要创建一个
navigation app or a fitness app,
比如说 导航 App 或健身类 App
the continuous background
那么持续后台位置
location is almost certainly
绝对就是
what you're looking for.
你所需要的
We wanted to ensure that this
我们想确保
functionality was exposed in
这个功能只能
only one place, and so in
在一处使用 所以在
watchOS 4 HKWorkoutSessions no
watchOS 4 中 HKWorkoutSessions
longer give your app access to
不会再给予你的 App
location in the background.
在后台获取位置的权限
Legacy apps will continue to
旧版的 App 仍然能运作
work, but when you link against
但当你连接到
the watchOS 4 SDK, you must
watchOS 4 SDK 时
adopt the continuous background
你必须采用持续后台位置
location API.
API
Otherwise, your app will be
否则你的 App
unable to access the user's
将不能获取用户的
location.
位置
Luckily, it's very easy to adopt
幸运的是 采用我们的 API
our API.
非常简单
There are simply three easy
只需要简单的
steps.
三步
First, you enable the
首先在后台模式下
LocationUpdates background mode.
开启位置更新
Simply navigate to the
在 Xcode 中切换到
Capabilities tab in Xcode,
Capabilities 标签
scroll down to Background Modes,
下滑至 Background Modes
and check the Location Updates
并在 Location Updates 框
box.
打钩
Second, you need to set the
第二你需要在
allowsBackgroundLocationUpdates
Location Manager 中
property to True on your
将 allowsBackgroundLocationUpdates
Location Manager.
属性设为 True
We recommend you only do this
我们建议你仅在
after the user has performed
用户进行了某项操作后
some action which requires --
进行这一步而这要求
sorry.
抱歉
Getting a little ahead of
我讲快了
We recommend you do this only
我们建议你仅在
after the user has initiated the
用户开始锻炼
workout session or the
或者导航时
navigation session.
进行这一步
That way you don't accidentally
这样你就不会
start the continuous background
在你打算开始之前
location session before you
启动了持续后台位置
meant to.
进程
Finally, you simply call
最后你只需要
startUpdatingLocation while your
当你的 App 在前台运行时
app is in the foreground.
调出 startUpdatingLocation
When your app enters the
当你的 App 进入后台时
background, Core Location will
Core Location 会让
keep your app running and
你的 App 保持运行
continue to deliver location
然后持续发送
updates.
位置更新
While we're talking about
当我们在讨论
workout apps, we have some
健身类 App 时
advice to help you create the
我们有一些建议能帮你
best possible experience for
为你的用户创造可能是最好的
your users.
体验
First, we recommend you continue
首先我们建议你
to use HealthKit, even though
继续使用 HealthKit
it's possible to create a
即使创建一个不使用
fitness app that doesn't use
HealthKit 或 HKWorkoutSession
HealthKit or HKWorkoutSession,
的健身 App 也是可能的
doing so will make your app miss
但这样做会让你的 App
out on a lot of special tuning
不能用上我们在 Core Location
we've put into Core Location for
中为健身场景设计的很多
workout scenarios.
调整
So continue to use HealthKit and
所以请继续使用 HealthKit 和
HKWorkoutSession.
HKWorkoutSession
Second, if you know that your
第二 如果你知道你的
user is in a pedestrian workout,
用户正在徒步锻炼
we recommend you use CMPedometer
我们推荐你使用 CMPedometer
to estimate how far the user has
来测算这个用户的行进
traveled.
距离
In some environments it can be
在某些环境下
very tricky to accurately
要准确计算用户的
estimate the user's location,
位置会非常困难
and if the user goes through a
如果用户在
run in one of those
这些环境中奔跑
environments, you'll find it's
你会发现
even harder to accurately
准确计算用户的
estimate how far they have
行进距离更加困难
But if you know they're in a
但如果你知道
pedestrian workout and you use
他们在徒步锻炼
CMPedometer, your app won't be
且你使用了 CMPedometer
affected by those difficulties.
你的 App 就不会被影响
Okay. That's the miscellaneous
好了 这些是零零碎碎
topics.
的事情
Let's get to the big one;
让我们来说重点
authorization and use of
授权以及报告的
reporting.
使用
We spent a lot of time iterating
我们花了很多时间来更迭
on how Core Location's
Core Location 的授权
authorization and usage
和使用报告的工作方式
reporting works, and we've got
我们尝试了一些
some exciting changes that we
令人兴奋的改变
think your users are going to
我们觉得你的用户会
love.
喜欢
First, let's quickly review how
首先让我们快速看一下
it all works.
它怎么工作的
Core Location supports two
Core Location 支持两种
authorization modes; WhenInUse
授权模式：WhenInUse
and Always.
和 Always
Always authorization allows your
Always 授权允许你的 App
app to access the user's
能在 App 运行的
location anytime your app is
任何时候获取用户的
running.
位置
Additionally, Always authorized
此外 Always 授权的 App
apps can use our background
可以使用我们的后台
monitoring API's.
监视 API
These allow your app to get
这些可以让你的
runtime and receive information
App 运行起来 并在有多个
when various location-based
基于位置的事件进行时
events have occurred.
接收信息
For example, the region
例如 每当用户
monitoring API will launch your
进入或离开了
app whenever the user arrives at
你指定的区域
or departs from a region of your
区域监测 API 就会启动
choosing.
你的 App
The WhenInUse authorization mode
WhenInUse 授权模式
allows your app to access the
允许你的 App
user's location anytime your app
在被使用的任何时候
is considered in use.
获取用户的位置
Usually if your app is in use,
通常如果你的 App 在使用期间
that means it's in the
意味着它处于
foreground, but that's not
前台但情况并不
always the case.
总是这样
For example, if you're using the
例如 如果你在使用
continuous background location
持续后台位置 API
API, on iOS Core Location will
在 iOS 中 Core Location
draw a blue bar, a blue
会绘制一条蓝色的状态栏
double-height status bar at the
在屏幕上方的两倍高度的
top of the screen, reminding the
蓝色状态栏 提醒用户
user that the app is still
这个 App 仍在
running and still accessing
运行并且仍在获取
their location, and in that way
他们的位置 这样
your app is still considered in
你的 App 就会被认作在使用
use.
中
We introduced the WhenInUse
我们引入了 WhenInUse
authorization mode because we
授权模式 因为我们
wanted to allow users a greater
想要让用户拥有
level of control over how apps
对 App 如何获取他们的隐私数据
access their private data.
的更高控制权
And users love this.
并且用户喜欢这样
They love knowing that apps can
他们喜欢知道 App
only access their location at
只有在他们想的时候
times when they want it to.
才能获取他们的位置
And we think this represents a
我们觉得这代表了
great balance between the user's
用户能控制你的 App
ability to control how your app
如何获取他们位置
accesses their location and your
与你能为用户创造
ability to create compelling app
具有吸引力的 App 体验
experiences for the user.
之间的良好平衡
Since we introduced the
自从我们引入了
WhenInUse authorization mode the
WhenInUse 授权模式后
response has been tremendous.
得到了热烈响应
Almost 80 percent of
iOS 中几乎百分之八十
location-using apps on iOS
使用位置的 App
support WhenInUse authorization.
支持 WhenInUse 授权
A mere 21 percent have chosen to
只有 百分之二十一 选择
require Always authorization
从用户那里获取
from the user.
Always 授权
Users love the WhenInUse
用户们喜欢 WhenInUse
authorization mode, and thanks
授权模式
to your efforts, they almost
多亏了你们的努力
always have it available to
他们几乎一直拥有
them.
选择权
We think this is fantastic, but
我们认为这非常棒
we wanted to see if we could do
但是我们想知道我们能不能
better.
做的更好
Now, let's look at some of the
现在让我们看看
reasons why an app might choose
一个 App 可能选择获取
to require Always authorization.
Always 授权的一些原因
We think that one of the common
我们认为其中一个常见
reasons is the developer's
原因是开发者只是
simply confused.
感到困惑
It turns out that many apps
事实证明许多
which require Always
要求 Always 授权
authorization don't actually use
的 App 实际上并未使用
any of our background monitoring
我们的任何一个后台监测
API's.
API
It's very likely that these apps
很有可能这些 App
would continue to function just
会继续正常运作
fine if they were granted
即使他们获得的是
WhenInUse authorization instead.
WhenInUse 授权
But when the user encounters one
但当用户遇到一个
of these apps, they don't know
这样的 App 时 他们并不知道
that.
这点
They can't see the app source
他们不能看见 App 的
code.
源代码
They don't know that it won't
他们不知道
monitor them all day and so they
它并不会监测他们一整天
have to treat it as though it
所以他们只能当做它会
will, and this creates a very
来对待 而这带来了
poor user experience.
非常差的用户体验
Now, a second reason we think
我们认为很多开发者
that many developers choose to
选择请求 Always 授权
require Always authorization is
的第二个原因是
they're simply trying to give
他们只是想给
their users the best possible
他们的用户最好的
experience.
体验
See, not all features can be
看 并不是所有功能
implemented reasonably with
都能恰当地用
WhenInUse authorization.
WhenInUse 授权实现
Some basically require Always
有些功能就是需要
authorization, and we think that
Always 授权
these developers simply want to
我们认为这些开发者只是
ensure that their users have
想确保他们的用户
access to all the best that
能得到 App 提供的
their app has to offer, but this
最佳体验 但是这对
makes for a very poor user
那些不希望给予
experience for the users that
App Always 授权
don't wish to grant the app
的用户带来了非常差
Always authorization.
的用户体验
They are forced to choose
他们被迫
between granting the app Always,
在授予 App Always
which is more than they would
和和授予其 Never 中作出选择
like in this example, or
就像在这里例子中 他们并不想这样
they don't get to benefit from
Never 意味着他们不能
any of the app's location-based
从 App 中任何基于位置的功能中
features.
受益
And their final openings to
他们最后授予其
grant it Always and then revoke
Always 然后在使用完
that authorization after they're
这个 App 后就撤销了
done using the app.
这个授权
In any case, the user is not
无论如何用户都没有
having a great time with this
和这个 App 相处得
app.
很好
So for iOS 11 we're asking all
所以在 iOS 11 中我们要求所有
developers with Always
拥有请求 Always 的 App
requesting apps to additionally
的开发者额外支持
support the WhenInUse
WhenInUse
authorization mode.
授权模式
This change is both retroactive
这个变化既具有回溯性
and forward-looking, so when the
又具有前瞻性
user updates to iOS 11, they
所以当用户升级至 iOS 11 后
will be able to authorize any
他们可以向任何
app that requests Always
请求 Always 授权的
authorization the WhenInUse
App 给予 WhenInUse
authorization mode instead.
授权模式
If you link against the iOS 11
如果你连接至 iOS 11 SDK
SDK, you must provide a
你必须提供
WhenInUseUsageDescription.
WhenInUseUsageDescription
Otherwise, your app will be
否则你的 App
unable to request Always
将不能请求 Always
authorization.
授权
Furthermore, when your app
此外当你的 App
requests Always authorization,
请求 Always 授权时
we will additionally display an
我们会额外显示
option to grant your app
一个选项来给予你 App
WhenInUse authorization instead.
WhenInUse 的授权
With these new three option
有了这三个新的选项
prompts we have a new
提示我们还有个新的
UsageDescription string as well.
UsageDescription 字符串
Your app needs to provide an
你的 App 需要提供一个
AlwaysAndWhenInUse
AlwaysAndWhenInUse
UsageDescription.
UsageDescription
Since this is a different key
因为这是一个不同的 Key
your app must provide it when
当你连接至新的 iOS 11
you link against the new iOS 11
SDK 时你的 App 必须
SDK.
提供它
For apps linked against iOS 11
对于连接到 iOS 11 和之后
and later, Core Location will
版本的 App Core Location
not use the old NSLocationAlways
不会使用旧的 NSLocationAlways
UsageDescription key.
UsageDescription Key
So let's talk a little bit about
让我们谈一下最佳实践案例
best practices; how does this
看看这个是怎么
change things.
做出改变的
For apps that want Always
对于想要 Always 授权
authorization we recommend you
的 App 我们推荐你
provide all three keys, even
提供所有三个 Key
that NSLocationAlways
包括 不会再用的NSLocationAlways
UsageDescription that I just
UsageDescription
said we won't use.
这个我刚说过
And the reason why is if you
因为如果你想
want to deploy your app on a
在一个运行 iOS 10 或
device that's running iOS 10 or
更早版本的设备上部署你的 App
earlier, you need to provide
你需要提供它能
strings that it can understand,
读懂的字符串
and so you should continue to
所以你应该继续
provide that NSLocationAlways
提供 NSLocationAlways
UsageDescription.
UsageDescription
Second, your AlwaysAndWhenInUse
第二你的 AlwaysAndWhenInUse
UsageDescription should help the
UsageDescription 应该帮助
user choose between Always and
用户选择 Always 还是
WhenInUse.
WhenInUse
We'll use it in context where
在有两个选项呈现
those are the two options
给用户的情况下
presented to the user.
我们会用到它
So your description should
所以你的描述应该
explain to the user what
向用户解释
features will be enabled if they
如果他们选择了 WhenInUse 授权
select WhenInUse authorization,
会开放什么功能
and then what additional
以及如果他们
features they'll receive if they
给予了你的 App Always 授权
choose to grant your app Always
他们会得到什么额外的
authorization.
功能
For all apps we recommend that
对于所有 App 我们建议你
you only request authorization
只在你真正需要的时候
when you really need it.
请求授权
If you wait to request
如果你在等待请求
authorization until the user has
授权直到用户进行了
performed some action which
某些操作要求
requires access to the location,
获取位置
then when the prompt appears,
那么当提示出现时
the user will have all the
用户有了他们需要的
context, all this intuitive
使用背景以及直观的理解
understanding that they need in
就能知道为什么
order to understand why your app
你的 App 想要
wants access to location.
获取他们的位置
This makes it much more likely
这让他们给予
that they'll actually grant your
你的 App 授权变得
app authorization.
更有可能
For apps that request Always
对于申请 Always 授权
authorization, there's a little
的 App 还有一点点
bit more to that.
要说一下
We recommend you request
我们建议你先
WhenInUse authorization first.
申请 WhenInUse 授权
Requesting WhenInUse
申请 WhenInUse
authorization is a little bit
授权更容易一点
easier, not asking as much from
从用户那里要求
the user, but there's more to it
尽可能少 除此以外
than that.
还有
We think your app should make
我们认为你的 App 应该让
WhenInUse its base experience,
WhenInUse 成为基本的体验
the first thing users encounter.
这是用户首先会遇到的体验
Then, after the user has had a
然后在用户已经深度
chance to explore your app and
体验了你的 App
get to know all of its features,
并且了解了所有功能之后
when they discover that one that
当他们发现其中
requires Always, they'll try to
一个功能需要 Always 时
turn it on and at that point
他们会试着打开 而在那时
your app can display a
你的 App 可以显示
transition prompt that requests
转换提示申请用
Always authorization on top of
Always 授权覆盖你
the WhenInUse authorization you
已经拥有的 WhenInUse
already have.
授权
When this prompt appears, the
当这个提示出现时
user will once again have that
用户会再一次有了他们
intuitive context they need in
需要的直观使用背景
order to understand why your app
来理解为什么你的 App
is requesting Always and they'll
要申请 Always 授权
be much more likely to grant it
他们就会更有可能将它
to you.
授予你
Let's see how that works.
让我们看看它是如何工作的
So when the user first launches
所以当用户第一次启动
your app, you'll have an
你的 App 你会处于
undetermined authorization
一个未决定的授权
state.
状态
From here you can request either
在这里你可以申请
WhenInUse authorization or
WhenInUse 授权或
Always authorization.
Always 授权
Let's see what happens if you
让我们看看如果你申请
request WhenInUse authorization.
Always 授权会发生什么
Core Location will display our
Core Location 会显示我们的
WhenInUse authorization prompt,
WhenInUse 授权提示
using your
在提示的
WhenInUseUsageDescription in the
主体上 使用的是你的
body of the alert.
WhenInUseUsageDescription
Depending on the user's choice,
根据用户的选择
you'll end up with either
你会获得
WhenInUse authorization or no
WhenInUse 授权或
authorization at all.
没有任何授权
After this point the user can
在这之后用户可以
freely go to settings and adjust
随意到设置中调整
your app's authorization value
你 App 的授权 达到
to whatever they like.
他们想要的值
But if the user has chosen to
但是如果用户选择给予
grant your app WhenInUse
你的 App WhenInUse 授权
authorization, which they
其实他们很有可能
probably will if you're
会这么做 如果你按照
following our best practices,
我们的最佳实践做的话
you can additionally request
你还可以额外申请
Always authorization.
Always 授权
When this happens, Core Location
此时 Core Location
will display a transition prompt
会显示转换提示
and will use that new
并会使用新的
AlwaysAndWhenInUse
AlwaysAndWhenInUse
UsageDescription string.
UsageDescription 字符串
From here the user can either
从这里用户可以给予
grant your app Always
你的 App Always
authorization or keep it at its
授权或使其保持
current WhenInUse value.
当前的 WhenInUse 值
After your app has requested
当你的 App 申请
Always authorization it will be
Always 授权之后它将不能
unable to request any further
再申请任何其他的
prompts.
提示
So let's go back to the start.
让我们回到一开始
What if you had requested Always
如果你已经在一开始
authorization at the very
比如当你的 App 启动时
beginning, right when your app
就已经申请了
launches, for example.
Always 授权了呢
The user will see this prompt.
用户会看到这个提示
They'll see a WhenInUse option,
他们会看到一个 WhenInUse 选项
they'll see an Always option,
会看到一个 Always 选项
and they'll see a Don't Allow
还会看到一个 Don't Allow
option.
选项
If the user doesn't understand
如果用户不能理解
why your app wants access to
为什么你的 App
location all the time, if they
要一直获取位置
don't have that context that
如果他们没有
we're recommending you provide,
我们建议你提供的背景信息
then it's very likely they'll
那么很有可能他们会
grant your app WhenInUse
给予你的 App WhenInUse
authorization instead, and if
授权 如果这发生了
that happens, you won't be able
你将不能在之后
to initiate a transition prompt
发起授权转换
afterwards.
提示了
Oh, and this prompt also uses
对了 这个提示也使用
that new combined
那个新合成的
UsageDescription key.
UsageDescription Key
Okay. Before we move on from
好了 在我们从授权讲到
authorization, I'm excited to
下一个话题前 我很高兴地
announce that on watchOS 4 Core
宣布在 watchOS 4 上
Location will support prompting
Core Location 能支持
for authorization directly on
直接在表上显示
the watch itself.
授权的提示
Previously --
之前
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
Previously, if you tried to
之前如果你想
request authorization, watchOS
申请授权
would alert the user that
watchOS 会提醒用户
there's a prompt waiting for
在他们手机上有个
them on their phone and they
提示等待他们处理
would have to go over to their
他们必须到手机上
phone and respond to it there.
在那里作出回应
We haven't got this all finished
我们还没有完成所有的
yet.
更新
It's not in the seed you
这不在你们这周早些时候
received earlier this week, but
收到的随机数种子里但是
we do expect it to land in a
我们预计会把它放到
future seed.
未来的种子里
When it's done, all you'll have
弄好后你需要做的
to do is rebuild your app and
只是重新构建你的 App
the next time you install it,
下一次你安装时
you should start to see these
你应该能开始看到这些
standalone prompts.
独立的提示了
That's authorization.
这是授权部分
Let's talk about usage
让我们来谈谈
reporting.
使用报告
But first, let's talk about how
但首先我们说说它如何
it worked in iOS 10.
在 iOS 10 上工作
Core Location would report the
Core Location 会基于
location usage of your app based
你正使用的什么服务
on which services you were
来报告你 App 的位置使用
using.
情况
Most services would result in
大多数服务会让你的
your app getting a solid arrow
App 在状态栏和
in the status bar and in
设置里显示一个实心的
Settings.
箭头
If you used the region
如果你使用了区域
monitoring service, you would
监测服务 相反你会
instead get a hollow arrow.
得到一个空心的箭头
And finally, if you were a
最后 如果你是一个
WhenInUse authorized app and you
WhenInUse 授权的 App
requested the continuous
然后你请求了
background location service, we
持续后台位置服务
would draw this blue
我们会画出
double-height status bar that
双层高度的蓝色状态栏
I've mentioned a few times.
这个我已经提到了很多次
We felt this system was very
我们觉得这个系统
good.
非常好
It served us well for a long
它为我们服务了
time, but we thought there was
很久但我们觉得
room for improvement.
还有提升空间
This system over-represents the
这个系统有力地代表了
privacy exposure of some of our
我们一些 API 的
API's.
隐私暴露
Let's compare two apps; one of
让我们比较两个 App
them using the significant
其中一个使用
location change monitoring
显著位置变化监测服务
service, and the other one using
而另一个使用我们的
our continuous background
持续后台位置
location service.
服务
Both of these apps will have a
这两个 App 都会持续
solid arrow continuously.
显示实心的箭头
However, the app using
但是使用
significant location change
显著位置变化监测
monitoring is going to receive
的 App 相比于使用
far less location information
持续后台位置的 App
than the app using continuous
会接收更少的
background location.
位置信息
The app using significant
使用显著位置
location change monitoring is
变化监测的 App
only going to get updates when
只有在设备移动了
the device has actually moved a
一段显著距离时
significant distance, and even
才会收到更新 即使这样
then, there's a rate limit on
在这之上还有速率
top.
限制
And so the app receiving
所以接收
continuous background location
持续后台位置的 App
is going to get far more
会得到更多的
location information, but they
位置信息 但他们
have the exact same usage
有完全一样的使用
reporting.
报告
Furthermore, we thought that
此外 我们觉得
Always authorized apps were
Always 授权的 App
missing out on the blue bar as a
错过了蓝色状态栏的
feature.
功能
Suppose you have a navigation
假设你有一个
app that is granted Always
获得了 Always 授权的
authorization.
App
If the user is in a navigation
如果用户正在导航
session, they probably want to
他们很有可能
be able to return to that very
想要在草草地使用完
quickly after briefly using
另一个 App 后快速返回
another app, but in iOS 10
但是在 iOS 10 中
Always authorized apps don't get
Always 授权的 App
this blue double-height status
没有这个两倍高度的蓝色
bar.
状态栏
We felt that these problems made
我们觉得这些问题
it difficult for users to
让用户很难
correctly interpret how apps
正确理解 App 是如何
were using their location.
使用他们的位置的
For example, let's consider
例如 让我们再
those two apps again; the
看看这两个 App
continuous background location
持续后台位置
and the significant location
和显著位置改变
change monitoring app.
监测 App
Suppose the user goes for a run
假设用户用
with the continuous background
持续后台位置 App
location app.
去跑步
They'll go on the run, they'll
他们去跑步
come back, they'll see the solid
他们回来 他们会一直
arrow the whole time, and when
看到实心的箭头
they look at their map, they'll
当他们看地图时
see every twist and turn they
就会发现他们每一步的
took.
轨迹
When they install that app that
当他们安装了使用
uses significant location change
显著位置变化监测的 App
monitoring, they'll see the same
他们会看到同样的东西
thing, a solid arrow.
也就是一个实心箭头
As far as the user is aware,
就用户所知
this app is probably receiving
这个 App 可能和他们的
the same amount of information
跑步轨迹 App 接收了
as their run tracking app.
同样多的信息量
So if users are misinterpreting
所以如果用户理解错了
our signals, we decided the best
我们的标志 我们决定
way to fix this was to adjust
最好的解决方法就是
how we indicate location usage.
对我们如何指示位置使用的方式做出调整
We have a new policy and we
我们有一个新政策
think you're going to like it.
我们觉得你们会喜欢
We've changed how the arrow
我们改变了箭头的
works.
运作方式
When your app requests location
当你的 App 从 Core Location
information from Core Location,
请求位置信息时
we display a hollow arrow.
显示空心箭头
When you actually receive
当你实际上接收
location information, we'll
位置信息时
switch that to a solid arrow for
我们将它变成一个实心箭头
a few seconds.
持续几秒
We'll go through an example of
我们待会儿会
how that actually works in just
演示一个例子来说明
a few moments.
实际情况如何
In addition, as you probably
并且你可能已经猜到了
guessed, we're bringing the blue
我们将双倍高度的
double-height status bar to
蓝色状态栏带进了
Always authorized apps that use
使用持续后台位置
the continuous background
服务的 Always 授权
location service.
App
Now, we expect that this new
现在我们期望这个
policy will help users
新政策会帮助用户
understand your app's location
更好地理解 App 的
usage more better.
位置使用
So let's see.
所以让我们敬请期待吧
Previously we had that hollow
之前我们有那个
arrow behavior and users came to
空心箭头行为 于是用户
understand that the hollow arrow
知道了空心箭头意味着
indicated that an app was using
一个 App 正在后台
location in the background, but
使用位置服务 但是
it wasn't continuously receiving
它没有持续接收
updates.
更新信息
It was receiving them
它可能在
potentially intermittently or
断断续续地接收更新
only when specific events
或只有当特定的事件
occurred, and so they understood
发生时 这样他们就知道
that this arrow represented
这个箭头代表
low-powered background
低功耗的后台
monitoring.
监测
We're now extending that
我们现在 将
understanding to all of Core
这个理解延伸至
Location's API's, and we think
Core Location 的所有 API
this is much better for you as
我们觉得这对
the developers as well because
开发者你们好多了
now users will be able to see
因为用户现在可以看到
exactly how much, or as the case
当你的 App 在后台
may be, how little information
运行时实际上
your app is actually receiving
接收了很多
when it's running in the
或某些情况下
background.
很少的信息
If you're using our background
如果你使用我们的后台
monitoring API's, you'll find
监测 API 你会发现
that you have a hollow arrow
你会多一个空心箭头
more and a solid arrow less, and
少一个实心箭头
we think this will help users
我们认为这会帮助
understand that your app is not
用户理解你的 App
actually receiving every single
实际上并没有每一天都在
step, every twist and turn
接收每一小步改变或者
throughout their day.
每一次大转折这样的信息
Okay. So let's look at how that
OK 让我们看看在实践中
arrow works in practice.
箭头是如何工作的
Here we have a test iPhone and
这里我们有一部测试 iPhone
it's currently at AT&amp;T Park and
它现在在 AT&T 服务系统中
let's suppose an app is using
让我们假设一个 App 正在
the Visit monitoring service.
使用 Visit 监测服务
The device has been stationary
设备在此处静止了
here for a long time and so
很长一段时间
we're displaying a hollow arrow
所以我们在状态栏
in the status bar because Core
显示了一个空心箭头
Location is not delivering new
因为 Core Location 没有
information to the app.
向 App 发送新信息
However, once the user gets up
但是一旦用户起身
and starts moving towards, let's
并开始朝向
say the Ferry Building, Core
Ferry Building方向移动
Location will detect that
Core Location 会检测到
departure event and alert the
这个离开行为并通知
app.
App
That will result in a solid
这会导致一个实心
arrow appearing in the status
箭头在状态栏
bar for a few seconds.
显示几秒
As the user continues their
当用户继续移动时
journey the arrow will return to
这个箭头会回归
its hollow state and it will
空心状态并且它会
remain hollow until Core
继续保持空心直到
Location detects an arrival
Core Location 检测到用户已经到达
After it detects that, it will
在它检测到这个之后
launch the app once again and
它会再次启动 App
the app will receive a solid
这个 App 会接收到
arrow that will linger for a
一个实心箭头并停留
couple of seconds, and then
几秒钟然后
after that it will remain hollow
之后它就会保持空心
until the user departs from that
直到用户从那个位置
location.
离开
We really hope that this new
我们真的希望这个
policy helps users better
新政策能帮助用户
understand exactly when and how
更好地了解你的 App
your apps are accessing their
何时以及如何获取
location, and we think that it
他们的位置信息 我们认为
will result in users no longer
这会使用户不再因为
blaming your app for things it's
你的 App 实际没做的事
not actually doing.
而责怪它
That's what we've got for today.
这就是今天我们要讲的内容
And just to recap, there are
回顾一下 我希望
three important points I want
你们记住重要的
you to remember.
三点
First, users have more control
首先 用户对于你的 App
over how your app accesses their
获取他们的位置拥有更多
location.
控制权
Specifically, users can now
具体来说 如果你请求的是Always 授权
grant your app WhenInUse
用户现可以给予你的 App WhenInUse
authorization if you request
授权
Now, we always recommend that
我们一直建议你
you communicate with the user
和用户沟通并
and help them understand why
帮助他们理解为什么
your app wants access to
你的 App 想要
location, but apps that request
获取位置 但是请求
Always authorization have an
Always 授权的 App
even greater responsibility.
有更大的责任
If the user doesn't understand
如果用户不明白
why your app wants access to
为什么你的 App 想要
Always authorization, then
Always 授权 那么
they're not likely to grant it
他们有可能不会
to you.
给你这个授权
They're likely to give you
他们反而很有可能
WhenInUse authorization instead.
给你 WhenInUse 授权
So you have that greater
所以如果你想要
responsibility if you want to
Always 授权那么
receive Always authorization.
你就承担了更大责任
And the best way we think that
我们觉得你和用户沟通的最佳办法是
you can communicate with the
帮助他们理解为什么
user to help them understand why
你要 Always 授权
authorization, the best way to
要最大限度地提高
maximize your chances of
你从用户那里获得
receiving Always authorization
Always 授权的机会
from the user is to give them
就是给他们
that context that I talked about
一个我之前谈到过的
earlier.
背景信息
Give them that intuitive
让他们直观地
understanding.
理解
Let them explore your app with
让他们用 WhenInUse 授权
WhenInUse authorization, and
探索你的 App
then when they try to enable
然后当他们试图
that feature that requires
启用需要 Always
Always authorization, then you
授权的功能时
initiate that transition prompt
然后你就发起转换提示
and they will almost certainly
他们在那时就几乎
grant your app authorization at
一定会给予你的 App
that time.
授权
Thank you for your time.
感谢你们参与
If you'd like to learn more, we
如果你们想了解更多
have some supplementary material
我们在网上有一些补充
online.
资料
We've updated our PotLoc app,
比如我们更新了 PotLoc App
for example, so you'll find
所以你会发现
that's got some new goodies for
有一些新的好东西
you.
和你分享
We also recommend you check out
我们还建议你看看
these related sessions.
这些相关会议
I've already mentioned the Core
我刚刚已经提到了
Motion one, but the Privacy
Core Motion one 但是
session from earlier this week
这周早些时候的隐私会议
was also very good and it has a
同样非常棒 并且它有
lot of great advice to help you
很好的建议来帮助你
build an app that respects the
构建一个尊重用户隐私
user's privacy.
的 App
Thank you for your time, and I
感谢你们的时间
hope you enjoy the rest of WWDC.
我希望你们开心度过接下来的 WWDC